download32.com 2001-02-03

# DownLoad32.com

**   
Business  
Development  
Education  
Games  
Graphics  
Info Management  
Internet  
Sound  
Shell & Desktop  
Utilities  
Web Authoring**

| 

>   
>  **DownLoad32.com Privacy Policy  
>  **  
>  DownLoad32.com and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information.
> 
> This site, Download32.com Shareware download site, uses the services of Engage for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To do this, Engage collects anonymous data through the use of cookies. To learn more about Engage, including your ability to opt out of the Engage system, go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy>.
> 
> **Visitor Information**
> 
> During the process of delivering an advertisement to you, DownLoad32.com does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, DownLoad32 does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by DownLoad32 is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of our advertisers.
> 
> If you would like additional information about the types of non-personally identifiable information that is collected by our partner Engage please [click here.](http://www.flycast.com/about_us/index.cfm?sub=pri&content=priv-coll)
> 
> In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information in response to a specific ad (this ad may ask you to fill out a survey or provide your zip code). If this does occur, we may collect this information on behalf of an advertiser. This information is used by an advertiser to respond to your request. In addition, we may combine this information with other users' information and review it in an aggregate form to understand the type of individuals who view a specific type of ad or visit a particular kind of website.
> 
> **Engage Profiles**
> 
> Engage Network Web sites use anonymous identifiers (“cookies”) to collect anonymous preference and interest information. This information is provided by Engage to Engage Technologies, Inc. (“Engage”) and is used by Engage to create anonymous interest profiles on individual browsers. This information does not include any personally identifiable data (such as name, address or e-mail address) that is considered sensitive or controversial or would compromise a consumer’s privacy. Engage profiles are accessed by Engage-enabled Web sites and marketers to tailor site content, promotions and advertising, and to perform market research. Engage allows consumers to opt-out from these profiles at any time. To do so, a user should visit [www.engage.com/privacy/koptout.htm,](http://www.engage.com/privacy/koptout.htm) where they can receive an “opt out tag” that disables their browser from being recognized by the Engage system. For more information on Engage go to [www.engage.com](http://www.engage.com/).
> 
> **  
>  Data Collection and Opt Out**
> 
> DownLoad32.com, as well as most sites on the Internet, uses "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web. DownLoad32.com cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. What are cookies and why do we use them? A cookie is a unique number that is provided to you the first time we serves you an ad. This unique number, which is stored in a cookie file on your computer, helps us target ads to you. This cookie can help Engage ensure that we don't serve you the same ad multiple times, and help our advertisers understand what you like and don't like about their offerings so that they can cater better to your needs the next time you are interested in their products or services. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience by limiting the number of times you see the same ad and delivering more relevant content to you, they are not required for Engage to deliver you an ad.
> 
> If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information.
> 
> **Opt Out Procedure**
> 
> If you would like to "opt out," that is, to prevent any data from being stored by Engage, please [click here](http://www.flycast.com/about_us/index.cfm?sub=pri&content=priv-optout).
> 
> **Participation in Industry-side Privacy Initiatives**
> 
> Engage is involved with several recognized trade associations and privacy groups that are both actively shaping privacy policies and support consumer privacy. Among these is the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), a group of third party ad networks dedicated to increasing consumer confidence in online advertising and the growth of the Internet economy. NAI is committed to providing users with a clear explanation of what data is being collected, how it is being used and why this is beneficial to a consumer's online experience. Additional information on NAI is available at [www.networkadvertising.org.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)
> 
> On November 8, Engage participated in a joint Federal Trade Commission and Department of Commerce workshop in Washington, D.C. Lyn Chitow Oakes, COO of Engage, testified at this workshop along with several other NAI members. They described for government officials and privacy advocates NAI’s efforts to develop a framework for self-regulation, and expanded upon NAI's principles of notice and choice. The group also used the forum to educate participants on the benefits of targeted advertising. Government officials listened to the group’s testimony, and we believe that it was well received. To view footage of the FTC workshop, [click here](http://www.flycast.com/about_us/index.cfm?sub=pri&content=priv-video).
> 
> We are also actively participating in the Direct Marketing Association's efforts to establish industry guidelines that safeguard the right to privacy, and are members of the Ad Club of New York, the New York New Media Association, the Interactive Advertising Bureau.
> 
> **  
> Contact us**
> 
> If you have any questions, tips or suggestions, feel free to contact us:
> 
> DownLoad32.com  
>  Boorstraat 11  
>  3371AA Hardinxveld  
>  Netherlands
> 
> Phone: +31 020  86 83 555  
>  Fax:     +31 020  88 48 752  
>  Email: [support@download32.com](mailto:support@download32.com)
>
>> |
